添酒
再来一杯
悠着点喝  先生
今天天气炎热
总是会让人心烦意乱
稍不慎就会怒气冲天
这个世界上有两种人
一种是喝酒的人
另一种是倒酒的人
闭上你的狗嘴  给我满上
喂  你们俩个
对  就是你们
我以前也跟你们一样
为老板埋头苦干
但后来不干了
因为我意识到在水龙头前排队等候
是永远无法喝饱水的
听他一句吧
你们会受益匪浅的
近来可好啊  老板
见到你真好啊  朋友
我从没想过你会有如此深的感触啊
我想我该写本书了
可以一试  可以一试
什么风把你吹到这个不起眼的小地方来啦
我就知道能在这里找到你
你没有东西要交付的吗
没时间了  不是吗
不急  有的是时间
玳瑁出门可能会晚
但他总能
第一个搞定
是啊  人如其名
我喜欢你说话的方式  玳瑁
是吗
你讲话的方式
就像瀑布一泻而下
我喜欢这样的你
我太笨了  居然错过了你的生日
不  我深感自责
所以我不远千里来此小镇
为你送上礼物
礼物么
算了  老板  别麻烦了
不麻烦  我乐意之至
我放在后面了
后面
是啊  来吧  跟我来
太赞了
你真的喜欢
爱死了
多么好的宠物啊
谢谢你  老板
好极了
我给你写上签名
写上
赠予侃爷
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧字幕 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
绝
命
毒
师
第三季
第三集
翻译：小路     meredith49     Silmar     泡泡龙     yank121
■
校对：独醉     时间轴：Angelica     特效：WiLL
后期：冰河       监制：蛐蛐
■
他还活着
He's still breathing.
看他的样子  似乎并不知情
By the looks of him, he has no idea how close he came.
我猜索尔·古德曼不必知晓
I'm assuming Saul Goodman doesn't need to know.
只字不提
Mum's the word.
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
稍等片刻  宝贝
Hang on, baby.
喂
Hello.
沃尔特  你在家里吗
Walt, are you in the house?
你好  斯凯勒
Oh, hey, Skyler.
对  我在家
Yeah, it's me.
你在搞什么鬼
What-- What the hell are you doing in there?
我搬回来了
I'm back.
不不  你不能搬回来
No. No, you're not back.
沃尔特  你不能搬回来
Walt, you're not back.
给  我  滚出去
Get-- Get-- Get out of there.
这也是我的家  斯凯勒
Well, it's-- it's my house, too, Skyler.
我要住这儿  就这样
I'm staying. End of story.
我们有过协议
We had an agreement.
我什么也没同意
I didn't agree to anything.
听着  先进屋吧
Now, look, just come on inside,
我们好好谈谈好吗
and we'll talk this through, okay?
不用了  我们之间没什么好谈了
No. No. There's nothing to talk about.
你不滚出去  我是不会踏进家里一步的
I am not coming in there until you get out.
好吧
Well...
你请自便
suit yourself.
沃尔特  沃尔特
Walt. Walt?
你发什么神经
What is wrong with you?
斯凯勒  我有权住在家里
Skyler, I have every right to be here.
不  你没有
No, you don't.
你不能再住这家了
You don't live here anymore.
我们离婚了
We're getting a divorce.
我没同意离婚
I don't agree to a divorce.
由不得你
It's not up to you.
如果你不马上离开
If you don't get out of here right now,
我就报警
I'm going to call the police
然后把一切都告诉他们
and I'm going to tell them everything.
我说到做到  沃尔特
I mean it, Walt.
电话在那边
There's the phone.
正在接通
It's ringing.
阿尔布开克警局
Albuquerque Police Department,
我是314B号话务员  有什么能为您效劳
Operator #314B. How may I help you?
阿尔布开克警局  有什么能为您效劳
Albuquerque Police Department, how may I help you?
我要报警  我被人骚扰
Yes, I-- I want to report a disturbance, please.
也不算是骚扰
No, no, it's not-- it's not exactly--
是
It's, um...
是家庭纠纷
It's a domestic issue.
好的
Okay.
他们正在询问我
They're connecting me.
我发誓  我会全盘托出
Right hand to God, I will tell them.
做你该做的吧  斯凯勒
Do what you have to do, Skyler.
这个家是我的一切
This family is everything to me.
失去了家  我还有什么好怕的
Without it, I have nothing to lose.
好吧
Fine.
喂  我叫斯凯勒·怀特
Yes, my name is Skyler White.
现在我家急需警察的帮助
I need police assistance at my home right away.
我的
My--
即将成为前夫的男人闯入我家
soon-to-be ex-husband broke into my house,
我需要警察来协助将他赶走
and I need an officer to come and remove him.
我的地址是尼格拉阿罗约路308号
It's 308 Negra Arroyo Lane.
好的
Okay.
多谢
Thank you.
他们马上就来了
They're coming.
爸爸回来啦
Oh... Dad's here?
爸爸
Dad.
好儿子  过来
Hey, son, come here.
你过得好吗
How are you?
你...你回来长住了吗
Are-- Are you back for good?
你...你怎么这么早就回来了
Why-- Why are you home so soon?
我...我没有啊
I-- I'm not.
我超饿  来点焗芝士三文治怎么样
Hey, I am starving. How about a grilled cheese?
-好啊  当然  -你也要一份吗
- Yeah, sure.  - You want one, too?
沃尔特  我和你爸爸有些事要谈
Walter, your dad and I have something we need to discuss.
你的三明治做好时
When your sandwich is ready,
我给你拿到你的...你的屋里
I'll bring it to your-- to your room.
妈妈  能等一等吗
Mom, can't it wait?
我感觉已经好久好久没有见过爸爸了
I haven't seen Dad in, like, forever.
沃尔特
Walter--
那你明天要去上班吗
So are you gonna be at work tomorrow?
是的  我打算去上班
Yeah, that's the plan.
你好  女士
Hello, ma'am.
我们来处理一起骚扰事件
We were called about a disturbance?
其实更准确说是擅自进入  但是...
It's more of a trespassing situation, really, but--
是的  是我报的警
Yeah, that was me.
你居然报警抓爸爸
You called the cops on dad?
我...我下班回家
I, uh-- I came home from work,
看见他回来了
and he was back.
他就这样搬回来住了
He just moved back into the house.
然后我叫他离开  但他不听
And I asked him to leave, but he won't listen.
我只是
I just--
我...我想让他离开
I-- I want him out.
我想让他离开这个家
I want him out of the house.
好的  怀特女士  有几个问题
Okay, Mrs. White. There's a couple of questions
需要你立刻回答
I need to ask you right off the bat.
你必须如实回答  这很重要
It's very important that you answer them honestly.
他打你了吗
Did he strike you?
没有
No.
他曾经打过你吗
Has he ever hit you?
没有  这和家庭暴力无关
No. This is not about violence.
只是擅自进入
This is about trespassing,
是他违背我个人意愿的擅自闯入
about him being here against my will.
好的  擅自闯入
Okay. Trespassing.
你们离婚了吗
You're divorced, then?
没有  正着手进行
No, working on it.
现在我们处于分居中
Right now we're separated.
法定分居吗
Legally separated?
如果你是指法院指令的分居  不是的
Well, there's not a court order, if that's what you mean,
但我们已经分居了两周左右的时间
but we've been living apart for almost two weeks, give or take--
我换了锁
I changed the locks.
难道这不算破门而入吗
Isn't that breaking and entering?
这栋房子归谁名下
Whose name is on the title to the house?
我们两个人的  是共同所有
Both of us. It's jointly owned.
我们不能因他闯入自己的房子而逮捕他
We can't arrest a man for breaking into his own house,
除非有法院指令
not without a court order
要求他远离上述房屋的情况
requiring he stays away from the premises,
又或者他曾以任何方式威胁你或孩子
unless he's threatened you or the kids in any way.
不  没有
No, not--
没有身体上的威胁  但让他留在这栋房子里
not physically, but having him in the house is just--
不是件好事
It's not a good thing.
-不好意思  -别哭了  爸爸在这儿呢
- Excuse me. - Don't cry. Daddy's here.
我来哄她  亲爱的
I got her, honey.
爸爸抱
Oh, come here.
这样好了吧
There we go.
你饿了吗
You hungry?
来吧
Here we go.
真乖
Oh, that was it.
我很抱歉  长官  我们说到哪儿了
I'm sorry, Officer. Where were we?
意见分歧
Disagreements.
是的  我们在很多事情上有争议
Yeah, so we've had our share of that.
我...我没有
Um, I-- I haven't...
近来  我不是一个体贴的丈夫
I haven't been the most attentive husband lately.
怀特女士  如果我们到外面谈的话
Mrs. White, would this be easier
对你来说会不会好受些
if we stepped outside for a minute?
不用了
No.
我在这儿很好
I'm fine right here.
我跟你说实话  女士
I'm gonna level with you, ma'am.
如果你想让你的丈夫离开这栋房子
If you want your husband out of the house,
你必须得和我合作
you're gonna have to help me out.
你是否知道  他有没有触犯过某条法律
Is it possible maybe he's broken any laws that you know of?
任何违法的事
Anything at all.
任何我们可以用到的  直说无妨
Anything that we can work with here, just tell me.
即使你认为他有犯法的嫌疑也行
Even if you've just got a suspicion of wrongdoing,
会有用的
I can work with that.
我能以此将他赶出去
I'll get him out of the house for you.
你对这事有什么看法吗
What's your take on all this?
是...是我妈妈的错
It-- It's my mom's fault.
我  她都没说过我爸爸做错了什么
I--she won't even say what my dad did
事实是他什么都没做错
and it's because he didn't do anything.
我不懂她为什么要这样
I don't know why she's being this way.
我的...我的爸爸
My-- My dad--
他是个好人
...he is a great guy.
怀特女士
Mrs. White?
我很抱歉  女士
I'm sorry, ma'am.
没有法律依据便不能将你的丈夫赶出去
There's no legal basis for us to remove your husband from the house.
下次你觉得事情要失控时
Next time you feel like things are getting out of control,
就打这个电话
you should call this number.
这是家庭专线
It's the family hotline.
我很愿意为你提供咨询
I'd really look into some counseling.
祝你们好运
Best of luck to you folks.
多谢  长官  抱歉让你们跑一趟
Listen, thank you, officers. We're sorry.
你为什么要...
Why do you got to...
你为什么要这么对爸爸
Why do you got to do this to Dad?
小沃尔特  等等
Jr.Wait. Come on.
不要怪你妈妈
Don't blame your mother for this.
对不起
Sorry.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
他还活着
He lives!
恭喜乔迁  小子
Happy housewarming, kid.
-看见我别这么开心  -谢谢
- Don't look so glad to see me. - Thanks.
装修不错
Interesting decor.
说来有趣
It's, uh, subtle.
我对简约艺术一直不感冒
The whole minimalist thing never really blew my hair back,
过得怎么样
So, how are you doing?
没吸毒吧
You staying clean?
很好
Good.
一直没有你的消息  我担心你
I was kind of worried that you were back to old habits,
旧瘾复发来着
since I didn't hear from you, you know?
你有没有意识到
Realize how stupid it is
不接自己律师的电话很愚蠢呢
to ignore your counsel's phone calls?
若我来电话警告你毒品缉私局
What if I was trying to warn you
要上门来抓你呢
that the DEA was going to kick down your door?
我是说  那可怎么办哪
I mean, what then, huh?
别拐弯抹角了
Why don't you spare me the sermon
直说你来干嘛吧
and get to why you're here?
好吧
Fair enough.
记不记得那天
Remember the other day
我跟你提过
when I brought up the idea
让你和老搭档联络联络
of you getting back in touch with your, uh, partner?
我想重新解释一下
Well, I kind of wanted to refloat that boat.
我没有让你继续制毒的意思
I'm not suggesting that you yourself get back to cooking,
我明白你金盆洗手了
I mean, you being in rehab and all.
我只是想让你  劝劝首席毒师重操旧业
I only want you to convince the master chef to do his thing,
你意下如何
So what do you say?
知道了  伙计  随你
Sure, man. Whatever.
别呀  什么随我
Okay. Whatever what?
你会不会给他打电话
I mean, you going to call him?
我说了  交给我了
I said I'll handle it.
走吧  成不
Now bounce, will you?
请吧
Please?
最后一句
Final thought.
看看这房子
Look at this place.
空无一物的
You're house poor.
你又没有经济来源
You got no bankroll.
你要是能让大毒师重新制毒
If you get the maestro cooking again,
我必有重谢
I'll make it worth your while.
打电话给他
Call him.
喂  如果你想向我推销东西
Hey, if you're trying to sell me something,
我给你四个字
I've got four little words for you...
谢绝推销
Do not call list.
如果不是呢  在嘀声后留言
However, if you're cool, leave it at the beep.
施拉德
Schrader.
是我  长官  什么事
Yes, Sir? Yeah, what's up?
是吗
Yeah?
真是好消息  谢谢长官
That's great news, Sir. Thank you.
好的  好的  当然
Ah, yeah, yeah. Absolutely.
那是一定的
You can bet on that.
再次谢谢你  长官
Hey, listen, thanks again, Sir.
非常感谢你帮我这个大忙
I really appreciate you stepping to the plate.
谢谢
Thank you.
你就打算让我蒙在鼓里吗
You going to keep me in suspense or what?
什么好消息
What's the good news?
默克特来电话告诉我好消息
Merkert called in a couple of favors.
埃尔帕索让我回去
El Paso wants me back. Aaah!
恭喜了老兄  太棒了
Hey, man, congrats, man. That's fantastic.
谢谢
Thank you.
你好
Hello.
先生们  欢迎光临
感谢你的到来
入境没遇到问题吧
我要是连边境都过不来  就该退休了
请进吧
抱歉这门不能走轮椅
我们很抱歉  古斯塔沃
我们本该事先通知你
这里是你的地盘  你要管辖无可厚非
但是
我们相信  那人与你并无瓜葛
可我们确实有关系
这么说  你和这位海森堡有生意来往咯
我不知道他还用过这个名字  但确有其事
我从不掩饰
我经常与本地制造商合作
我们俩仍然一同谋利
此事绝不会影响到我们的关系
塞拉曼加老师有一个叫屠库的侄子
我有耳闻
那你该知道  塞拉曼加老师亲自教他入行
待他亲如己出
后来塞拉曼加老师年老  屠库继承他的衣钵
他是我们集团在边境线北边的重要人物
非常忠诚
这位海森堡  沃尔特·怀特
是屠库的本地供货商之一
可是他背叛了屠库
现在  你该了解了  血债必须血偿
这是屠库的两位堂兄弟
他们有权报仇雪恨
塞拉曼加家族和我们集团
在这个问题上的观点是一致的
塞拉曼加老师
先生们
我能理解你们的悲恸
请你们节哀
我承认  你们确实有权利复仇
但我现在  仍与此人有生意上的合作
等我把生意做完
他便不再与我有任何瓜葛了
在那之前
我需要他活着
借一步说话
古斯塔沃  我不干涉你怎么炸鸡排
你也不该干涉我集团的政策
那我的地盘我就不管了吗
当然也要管
我会让他们耐心些
但我也劝你尽快搞定和这个家伙的生意
稍有不慎他就会影响到我们的合作关系
那样可不明智啊
里面那两个男人
我也不敢保证他们能听我的话
可不像你我这般理智
喂  如果你想向我推销东西
Hey, if you're trying to sell me something,
我给你四个字
I've got four little words for you...
谢绝推销
Do not call list.
如果不是呢  在嘀声后留言
However, if you're cool, leave it at the beep.
喂  如果你想向我推销东西
Hey, if you're trying to sell me something,
我给你四个字
I've got four little words for you...
谢绝推销
Do not call list.
如果不是呢  在嘀声后留言
However, if you're cool, leave it at the beep.
喂  如果你想向我推销东西
Hey, if you're trying to sell me something,
我给你四个字
I've got four little words for you...
亲爱的
Oh, swtheart.
宝贝对不起  对不起
Oh, sweetie, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
没事  没事了  宝贝
It's okay. It's okay, my girl.
好了  没事了
Oh, yes. It's okay.
没事了  妈妈就在这
It's okay. Mama's got you.
妈妈就在这
Oh, Mama's got you, yeah.
睡吧睡吧
Yes. Oh.
斯凯勒  要我帮忙吗
Skyler, want some help?
斯凯勒  我能用下洗手间吗
Skyler, can I use the bathroom?
我的老天
God.
你说的什么意思  跟你作对吗
What do you mean? Against your will?
是的  还相当顽固
Yes. Very much against my will.
他突然就回来了
He just...He...he showed right back up,
而且他也不同意离婚
and he...he doesn't want a divorce.
毫不犹豫的反对了
Won't even consider it.
我甚至打电话让警察带他走
I...I called the police on him.
我甚至差点就
I...I was...I was so close...
差点怎么了
So close to what?
没什么  算了
Nothing. Never mind.
斯凯勒  如果你不告诉我真相
Skyler, I can't advise you properly
我无法帮到你
if you don't give me all the facts.
根据律师与当事人的保密协议
Understand I am bound by the attorney-client privilege
我必须为你守口如瓶
to keep everything you tell me a secret.
未经你同意  我不会泄露只字片语
I can't tell a soul unless you authorize me to.
就算是非法的  你也可以保密吗
Even if it's something illegal?
非法的事  尤其保密
Especially if it's illegal.
我是你的律师  不是警察
I'm your lawyer, not the police.
我的工作就是保护你
My job is to protect you.
我丈夫私造甲基苯丙胺
My husband makes meth.
就是冰毒
Methamphetamine.
你丈夫是毒贩
Your husband's a drug dealer.
他只是生产毒品
A manufacturer.
在行话里
Technically, they, uh,
叫做毒师
they-- they call them cooks.
我是在网上找的
I looked it up on the Internet.
我给你个忠告  并希望你能听取
This is my advice, and you should take it.
马上向法院申请离婚
Sue your husband for divorce immediately.
然后我就到警局
Let me go to the police
举报你刚才告诉我的事
and tell them what you've just told me.
我这边呢
I'll go in ex parte
最快今天就能拿到法院的限制令
and get a restraining order from the court today.
只要他企图接近你或你的孩子
If he comes anywhere near you and your children,
无需多言  立刻被抓进监狱
he goes straight to jail, no questions asked.
毋庸置疑
This is a no-brainer.
这样做对你和你的家庭最有利
It's the best thing for you and your family.
不行
I can't.
我做不到
I can't do it.
我不想让我儿子发现
I don't want my son to find out
他的父亲是个罪犯
that his father is a criminal.
我只是
I just...
我不能这样对他
I can't do that to him.
到最后可能就由不得你了
In the end, it may not be up to you.
毒贩终究逃不过法律制裁的
Drug dealers have a way of getting caught.
沃尔特患有肺癌
Walt has lung cancer.
治疗虽然控制住了他的病情
His treatment bought him some time,
但医生们都说
but the doctors, they all say
迟早他都会...
that sooner or later--
连我自己都不清楚
But I can't see why
为什么家里发生了这些事
I should lay all this on my family
但我却
when...things may...
让其放任自流
resolve themselves on their own
而又不惊动其他人
without anyone else knowing.
伙计  我跟你打赌输了钱吗
Man, did I lose a bet or something?
干嘛要带我来这种地方
What are we doing in this shore?
没事的  放轻松
Just relax, will you?
放轻松  在这种鬼地方稍有不慎就被捅死
Relax? This is the kind of place you get knifed.
来这还不如去"小辣椒"
We should have went to Chili's, man.
伙计  既来之则安之
All right, already. Jesus.
牛排餐厅也不错
Outback Steakhouse.
现在去也不晚啊
It's not too late.
他们那有开胃洋葱条
They got that Blooming Onion.
偶尔吃点辣的有什么关系呢
What's wrong with spicing things up a little bit, huh?
这辣椒像被人吃过一样恶心
This spice looks like it's been through a couple of guys already.
你准备什么时候回埃尔帕索
So when are you headed back down to El Paso?
你知道
Uh, you know,
打包收拾再交接班
between the packing and errands and, uh,
再把事情安排好  估计还得一两周吧
getting my ducks in a row, maybe, um, a week or two.
还要一两周  拜托  伙计
A week or two? Come on, man.
要是我早麻利地回去了
I'd be dying to get back in the action.
是啊  但这边也还有工作要做完啊
Yeah, well, it's not like there's nothing going on up here.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
这里能有什么事
There ain't jack going on up here.
风平浪静
It's quiet as hell.
我去洗把脸
I'm going to hit the head.
那边的两个家伙
Those two over there.
我觉得他们身上有货
I think they're holding.
伙计  这种鬼地方  酒保身上都可能有货
Man, in this place, the bartender's probably holding.
你干什么
Whoa. What are you doing?
打给本地警方  还能干什么
Calling APD. What do you think?
难道我俩还搞不定两个小喽啰
Since when can't we handle a couple of dirtballs?
拜托伙计  好歹做做样子
Come on, man. Courtesy call.
万一是上头派的卧底呢
What if Vice is running some kind if undercover op?
见鬼
Screw it.
该你请客了
It's your turn to pay.
你干什么去
Where are you going?
我去上厕所
I have to take a leak.
天  你该吃点坦洛新了[前列腺药物]
Jesus, get yourself some Flomax.
站起来
Stand up.
你是看我们哪里不爽  贱人
Do you got a problem with us, bitch?
你一动我就不爽
Your move.
毒品缉私局  都不许动
DEA! Don't move.
去把我搭档给我叫进来
Go and tell my partner to get his ass in here.
喂  如果你想向我推销东西
Hey, if you're trying to sell me something,
我给你四个字
I've got four little words for you...
谢绝推销
Do not call list.
如果不是呢  在嘀声后留言
However, if you're cool, leave it at the beep.
喂  如果你想向我推销东西
Hey, if you're trying to sell me something,
我给你四个字
I've got four little words for you...
谢绝推销
Do not call list.
您所呼叫的区号为505
The number you have reached 1494985
号码为1494985的用户已停机
in area code 505 is no longer in service.
斯凯勒
Skyler.
我们能谈谈吗
Can we talk?
辖区负责人想要见你
ASAC wants to see you.
还有呢
And?
我们本来持观望态度  毒品交易发生后
We're hanging back. Saw a deal go down.
我去外面请求支援
I went outside to call it in.
你在这里盯着疑犯
You stayed to keep an eye on the suspects.
就是那时他们袭击了你
That's when they attacked you.
我没有告诉他们
What I didn't tell them
你在回里面去之前
is that you left your gun under the seat
把枪放在了座位下面
before you went back inside.
我做了件可怕的事情
I've done a terrible thing,
可我是出于好意
but I did it for a good reason.
为了这个家
I did it for us.
这是  小沃尔特的大学学费
That... is college tuition for Walter Junior
霍莉十八年的抚养费
and Holly, 18 years down the road.
还有你和孩子的医疗保险费
Then it's health insurance for you and the kids,
小沃尔特的物理治疗的费用
for Junior's physical therapy,
还有他的"学术水平测试"的家教费
and his SAT tutor.
买生活用品和汽油的钱
It's money for groceries and gas,
办生日派对和毕业派对的钱
for birthdays and graduation parties.
斯凯勒  这些钱
Skyler, that money
也是为了让你有瓦遮头
is for this roof over your head,
我死了后  单凭你做兼职会计
the mortgage that you are not going to be able
是无法还房屋贷款的
to afford on a part-time bookkeeper's salary when I'm gone.
-沃尔特  我  -你收下吧
- Walt, I-- - Please.
请你收下吧
Please.
这笔钱  不是我偷来的
This money... I didn't steal it.
不属于其他任何人
It doesn't belong to anyone else.
我赚来的
I earned it.
我为了赚这些钱所做的事情
The things I've... done to earn it...
我不得不做的事情
the... the... things I've had to do,
我不得不接受并适应的事情
I've got to live with them.
斯凯勒
Skyler.
我所做的一切
All that I've done,
我为这个家庭所做的所有的牺牲
all the sacrifices that I have... made for this family,
如果你不肯接受我赚的这些钱
all of that will be for nothing
我所有的牺牲都白费了
if you don't accept what I've earned.
请你接受吧
Please.
我会在这里等你下班
I'll be here when you get home from work.
你可以那时再告诉我答案
You can give me your answer then.
斯凯
Hey, Sky.
要来杯咖啡吗
Uh, some coffee?
好的
Yeah.
报告看上去挺不错的
That report's looking real good.
-报告不错  -那就好
- That-- I like how it looks. - Good.
你的孩子都在家吗
Are your kids home?
你好  怀特夫人
Hello, Mrs. White.
你好  路易斯
Oh. Hi, Louis.
非常感谢你们让我在这里吃晚饭
Hey, uh, thanks for having me over for dinner.
不客气
Um, sure.
斯凯勒
Hey, Skyler.
我正在做晚饭
I'm, uh, cooking dinner.
炖肉
Pot roast.
你能不能
Uh, could you--
你今天过得怎么样
So how was your day?
挺好的
Good.
挺好  非常好
Good. Excellent.
希望你不介意
I hope you don't mind.
我邀请了路易斯今晚一起吃晚饭
I invited Louis to stay for dinner tonight,
作为替我们送小沃尔特去学校的答谢
you know, as a thank you for driving Walter Junior to school for us.
我们都没在
We've been kind of absent,
不过我可以告诉你
but I tell you,
路易斯可帮了大忙
Louis really pitched in.
我只是想说我
Look, I just want to say that I--
我对早上我们之间的谈话感觉挺不错
I feel good about our talk this morning,
而且我也很想知道
and I'm-- I'm very eager to hear
关于我们谈论的话题你到底是怎么想的
what you're thinking about-- about what we talked about.
当然
But, you know,
你想要什么时候说都行
whenever you're ready, of course.
诚实挺好的  你不觉得吗
Honesty is good. Don't you think?
好了
There.
我和泰德上床了
I fucked Ted.
孩子们  吃晚饭了
Boys, dinner.
-谢谢  -路易斯
- Thank you. - Louis?
-是的  请给我点  -好的
- Uh, yes, please. - All right.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们俩都要把沙拉吃完  好吗
I want you boys both to eat your salad, okay?
好的
Okay.
我知道
I know.
没人喜欢沙拉
Nobody likes salad,
不过对你们的身体有好处
but it's good for you.
-谢谢  亲爱的  -谢谢你
- Thanks, darling. - Thank you.